{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"TV \u0026 Speaker Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46395/":{"taskOID":46395,"originalTaskOID":46395,"setID":1308,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6405,"questionDisplayText":"Component to repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What component needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8711,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Television","answerDisplayText":"Television","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8712,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8713,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8714,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8715,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503033,"questionDisplayText":"How old is the component?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the component?","shortQuestionText":"How old is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 years","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2- 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2- 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 4 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6407,"questionDisplayText":"Type of TV","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If you need a TV repaired, what kind of TV is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8720,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CRT","answerDisplayText":"CRT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8721,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"LCD","answerDisplayText":"LCD","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8722,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plasma","answerDisplayText":"Plasma","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8723,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Rear projection","answerDisplayText":"Rear projection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6405,"questionDisplayText":"Component to repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What component needs repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8711,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Television","answerDisplayText":"Television","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8712,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8713,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8714,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8715,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8711,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Television","answerDisplayText":"Television","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8712,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Projector or Screen","answerDisplayText":"Projector or Screen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8713,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DVD Player","answerDisplayText":"DVD Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8714,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"CD or Audio Player","answerDisplayText":"CD or Audio Player","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8715,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Speakers","answerDisplayText":"Speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8716,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","answerDisplayText":"Other Home Theater Accessory","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503033,"questionDisplayText":"How old is the component?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is the component?","shortQuestionText":"How old is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 years","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2- 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2- 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 4 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 years","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2- 4 years","answerDisplayText":"2- 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8719,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 4 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 4 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6407,"questionDisplayText":"Type of TV","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If you need a TV repaired, what kind of TV is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8720,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CRT","answerDisplayText":"CRT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8721,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"LCD","answerDisplayText":"LCD","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8722,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plasma","answerDisplayText":"Plasma","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8723,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Rear projection","answerDisplayText":"Rear projection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8720,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"CRT","answerDisplayText":"CRT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8721,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"LCD","answerDisplayText":"LCD","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8722,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plasma","answerDisplayText":"Plasma","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8723,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Rear projection","answerDisplayText":"Rear projection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8725,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46395/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46395,"taskName":"TV or Home Theater Accessory - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair TV or Home Theater Accessory","xmTaskDescriptor":"TV \u0026 Speaker Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":130,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"TV Theater Playstation Xbox Display","textMessagingName":"TV Repair","rolloverLongDesc":"Repairs TVs, and Home Theater Accessories.  Components repaired include Xbox, Playstation, DVD Player, CD Players and other electrical equipment.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair of TVs and Home Theater Accessories","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a TV or Home Theater Accessory.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"TV Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Speakers, TV Screens, DVD Players \u0026 More","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":6,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Repair TV or Home Theater Accessory","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"TV or Home Theater Accessory Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your TV Repair Project","urlName":"TV-or-Home-Theater-Accessory-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best TV, Screen \u0026 Speaker Repair Shops - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"TV,Theater,Playstation,Xbox,Display,projector,CD,Broken,Player,Television,DVD","emcCategoryOid":-12006,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1308,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}